rela my eyes flashing
lights good morning ladies and gentlemen
today is a very special day why you may
ask well because I need to make money I
need to make money it's a new year
shit's getting expensive and I need to
make money to buy another super
car Wait Alex but if you need money why
do you need it for a super because I
need it I need the rush rushing through
my veins of me buying a new car it just
does something makes me feel taller it
literally does this to me when I buy a
new superc car I go from being 62 to
being 6'4 and 2 in is a lot you guys
know that you know so this video I'm
going to be showing you guys every
single trade on how I'm going to break
down me going from not having a daily
from my daily from my daily from my
daily for my daily to then where I'm
able to do that just this week alone
from these trades by the way we are in
my new office I don't know if you guys
can see the difference this is not where
I was last time and I have two offices
in this house house tour coming soon and
second house tour coming soon but
updates on that in just a little bit you
keep say saying that I know but it's
okay cuz we will do soon so we're going
to start off this week to kind of get my
poor man Supercar poor man super car is
anywhere from 2 to 300K anything above
that then you become an average Supercar
owner if you own a Supercar below to
300K you're a [__] and you're poor
you're not there yet you have not made
it you're just not even in the 1% so I'm
going to teach you how to barely be part
of the 1% just this week alone with
these trades that we're going to be
analyzing today so the first one is
going to be CAD JPY CAD JPY currently on
the daily time frame has a very strong
accumulation level at this level of
support support support and resistance
whenever we're under we're going down
whenever we're above we're going up now
we're under it and we've had a
accumulation for about 10 days now the
daily time frame is indeed breaking
above this but the daily time frame
still has about 6 hours and 50 minutes
to close and as you guys can see up here
it's currently January 6th 10 in the
morning so we're going to be waiting for
this to close in about 6 hours and then
if it closes above I'm no longer
interested if it closes under I'm going
to be waiting for the break and retest
under this area to then sell next we
have AUD JPY where we are currently
having a lower low lower high lower low
now we're technically bullish higher
high but it looks like we're creating
this inverted Head and Shoulders left
head potential right shoulder what I
like is that we're at this level of
resistance so support resistance and
resistance we're using the EMA as
resistance as well and the daily time
frame is currently having a high push to
reject potentially reject this area once
again right here so what I'm going to be
waiting for in order to enter this trade
is going to be for some type of price
action like this on the 4 Hour you
notice whenever we're up here we have
rejection candlesticks then we sell
rejection candlesticks and then we sell
I want my rejection candlesticks yes
that is indeed a 4-Hour dogee it is a
rejection Candlestick but I need a
bearish Candlestick for me to confirm it
so then I can sell so I'm going to be
waiting for entries on this very soon
GBP CAD is probably by far my favorite
and I was literally about to enter it
before we started this video and I'm
glad I didn't cuz I would be in some
draw down that is because a daily time
frame you have a very strong left head
right shoulder price is coming back up
to retest this neckline of the head and
shoulders and on the 4our you guys can
see how we haven't really made it back
up to that area of Interest like it's
barely Wicked in to retest this
structure level right here so I want to
enter my trade up here if you notice I
have my alarm set up there I was going
to take an impulsive trade here but
truthfully my stop loss would have been
at a point where if it would have been
hit I was not fully wrong about the
trade I would have gotten Wicked out in
the position I was like entering a trade
where I if I put my stop loss and then
it gets hit I am completely wrong and
then the trade should have completely
reversed but this has not happened as of
right now so I'm going to be waiting for
price to make it up to here and not
enter this impulsive trade that's going
on and lastly is going to be gbpnzd on
the daily time frame we've had a very
strong double top at this very strong
level of resistance daily broke under
this neckline I'm going to be waiting
for the retest of this area for us to
then sell on the 4our we are then going
to be waiting for price to come back and
retest this EMA retest this level of
support support support to be used as
resistance to then sell so to show you
guys right now we're going to make a
quick anywhere from 2 to 300K this is my
account that I'm using right now as you
guys can see this is a $2 million
account this is the history and as you
can see it is a live account from lq so
you guys can go check them out Link in
the bio that's the broker that I've been
using lately and I trust them there's
thousands of differ of Brokers you guys
can go use whichever ones you want I
like this one they give me the leverage
that I want and I can go in and out with
crypto which is perfect so no trades as
of right now it is currently 10:12 in
the morning and uh let's see honestly I
think that we should shoot for like 400k
maybe we go a little bit higher than a
poor man super car right like why be a
one and be Guru right all right good
morning ladies and gentlemen it is
currently
8:53 January 7 7th
at a current $339,000 drop down now now
let me
explain sometimes before you win you got
to lose we're not losing though we're in
draw them a losing trade is not a losing
trade until it's a losing trade a
winning trade is not a winning trade
until it's a winning trade meaning it is
not losing until you don't close it it
is not one until you don't close it so
if you're in draw down right now if you
hold for forever you technically never
lose because you never closed remember
that it's like if you put it in but you
don't take it out did you really put it
in you're you're still in there exactly
so you never took it out so you never
really put it in that's what I'm saying
the point is that we took our first
[__] trade so right now we have GBP
CAD which is our first position onto the
market we took it about 15 minutes ago
so this is the trade that we were having
retest this left head and then the right
shoulder came back retested the EMA
retested the area of Interest kind of
did a little double top and then on the
1 hour we had a perfect shift of
structure so to me this was the little
bullet structure upwards we shifted it
right at this point Loki entered at the
bottom of the move but it's okay because
now we're having a pullback and we
decided to risk on this position
anywhere from about 100 10 to
$120,000 and if we catch a 1 to
2.5 then we can just do very simple math
which I'll do it for you guys right here
so we'll do
$130,000 times
2.5 will make anywhere about
$325,000 so that is a positive risk to
reward I'm winning more than I am
risking so for now we're just in a
little bit of draw down and all we got
to do is just set and forget and let's
see where the trade takes us so we'll
update you guys all right guys trade
update what is it I think it's like 2 3
hours later and we are currently up
$30,000 so we were actually down I think
almost 100 Grand like we got very close
to our stop loss if you guys can see
right here in the chart you guys can see
from when we entered the trade right at
this point price came all the way back
up almost stopped us the [__] out and
now we are in profit so literally
sometimes you enter a trade as soon as
you enter it which is this is actually
how it looks like right here as soon as
you enter it it can literally go
straight into your stop loss and then go
straight into your profit the issue that
a lot of Traders do is that they have
their stop loss too tight and then you
guys get stopped out and then it goes
straight into profit because you guys
don't know how to properly place your
stop loss properly placing your stop
loss is what will not only keep you in
the game game but make you actually have
winning traits because if your stop-
losses are too tight and you're going to
have the best trade set up with the best
confluences everything in your favor but
you have a 10 pip stop- loss you're
being unrealistic the market is going to
move 10 Pips just to create a movement
so it can go in your favor having the
right stop loss and set and forgetting
until the trade is your takeprofit is
what got me to become very successful in
trading and it's what's going to get me
my 300K
hopefully by today or tomorrow to buy
the poor man superar so for now we have
this beautiful 4-Hour bearish engulfing
Candlestick that is rejecting the EMA
Wick filling here that closes in about
an hour and a half which as soon as this
Candlestick closes I believe it's going
to have a small retracement and then
continue heading to the downside so
right now it is 1134 in the morning New
York session strong volume is going to
start slowing down in the next hour hour
so probably won't do an update until
later into London session so we'll
update you guys then last update as of
right now we're up
45k good morning ladies and gentlemen
um all I can say it
is 8 in the morning
January 8th and
boys we [__] did it we currently have
just [__] closed the account we are
now at $2.4 million on the account and
you guys can see the trades right here
in real time we have closed with a
$400,000 in profit the trade literally
from the last moment that I updated to
this very moment right now it basically
went straight into takeprofit and I did
not ever put a takeprofit because
obviously set and [__] forget but
this is going to be a perfect example on
why I never actually put the takeprofit
numbers it always ends up paying off
more than not so let me show you guys so
just to show you guys this is the exact
same account you guys can see right here
in the trade history area we are at 2.4
million same history same account Alex
Gonzalez with lq markets and this here
as well you guys can see when I entered
the trade you guys can see the history
you guys can see the swap you guys can
see the times you guys can see the stop
loss but no [__] take profit
because why would I want to minimize my
profit when I know where it's going to
go I don't really know but I have a very
high idea of where it's going to go
during the rest of the week by the way
this is the broker that I am using lqh
markets.com you guys can go check it out
click the link right here right now
currently I don't have a VPN on so when
I refresh it it tells me oh no my VPN is
on tells me that I am able to obviously
use it if you're in the US you got to
use a VPN to access this website cool so
now back to the charts you guys can see
that this trade we entered it went
straight into drw down as soon as we
entered it price went almost stopped us
out by I don't know I'd like to say 10
Pips not even like five Pips by that
Wick right there luckily our stop- loss
placement was done correct then from
that very moment from the very moment on
price just continued to go to the
downside then you can see over here that
price rejected perfectly the neckline of
this left head right shoulder created
that double top rejection from the EMA
and boom my first take profit was
originally set at this area here for a 1
to
2 6 1 to 2.5 but I always just place the
risk to reward tool so when price gets
there I want to see if I'm going to
decide if I'm going to close or not
because if I have this ginormous pattern
of a head and shoulders and then on the
daily time frame I have this ginormous
pattern the trend bearish as well I have
two time frames in sync letting me know
that this price is going to go to the
downside why would I not want to
continue to hold my trade especially if
the lower time frame structure on the
way to my takeprofit which is this area
here is still continuing structure why
would I minimize my profits well
truthfully if I would have seen this
when I was awake I would have probably
closed it at this point but I just
happened to wake up at 7 no I woke up
like at 8:15 or 8:30 and price was
already here and I said oh [__] I'm
going to close price right there because
I would have probably closed it at this
area here if I was awake and seing that
humongous rejection from that big red
Candlestick I would have thought it was
going to reject this area to have a
pullback to then continue going to the
downside I probably just wanted to get
my profits and go but I decided that as
soon as I woke up to just close at that
very moment I think that this from this
point here is going to then have a
retracement and then continue going to
the downside but I don't care I already
got exactly what I needed which is my
one two three risk to reward once again
you guys can see it right here and just
a document I also got it in my pictures
so you guys can see me closing this
trade live or at 7:30 in the morning so
as soon as I I'm not going to lie
there's a good thing to wake up to
waking up at 7:30 in the morning and
seeing you're up 400k in
profit it's a good fing I'll tell you
that so yeah that's basically all the
trades and I'm sure a lot of you guys
that are part of the channel you guys
see me take trades like this all the
time and you're like Alex you did
nothing different on this trade to make
make
$400,000 and it's like yeah I'm not
supposed to do anything different to
make $400,000 I've been making millions
of dollars in trading using a specific
approach if it's making me money why
would I change that approach I'm doing
the same approach until that [__] stops
working all I did was throw a little bit
more risk and do something with the
money so I think it's time now that we
go get respectfully my poor man Supercar
and you know what my budget was a/4 mil
300K now we're going to raise that
budget just a little bit let's raise it
just a little bit and let's get
something a little more interesting all
right ladies and gentlemen the time has
[__] come to get the new car the
driveway is a little empty the garage I
just have my motorcycle in there which
is actually decoration you know I'm
going to actually put that as decoration
in the back here now that I just
remember it right now yes we're going to
do that what car should we take should
we take the Bugatti
C7 cullin we can't show you these new
cars that we have here cuz these are
very lowkey but which one do you want to
take col cuz you want to dri yeah right
yeah so you drive I'm not driving i'
rather not deal with the liability here
you go ahead go yeah it's not a just
it's like a quarter of a liability right
no a lot less cuz the car is worth the
Bugatti is worth 3 million so a quarter
would
be [__] so it's actually not even a
quarter of a risk so even great decision
man you're you're actually like at an
18% 20% risk good decision bro R nice oh
what is that Bud he's packing yeah this
is uh this is my laddin lunch boox right
here as you guys can see I do not have a
bougie Chef not because I don't want to
because I have a keban chef and she
cooked for me and gives it to me like
this in a [__] wend Dixie Marshalls
bag but the food that in there is busted
respectfully you know why cuz I'm
getting [__] swo you want to see you
want to see look let me show
watch [__]
ready okay hold on you work on Amazon or
something what's that package I mean
know this is this [__] is real as [__]
like bro no one's going to take you
serious with that oh they won't take me
serious with this [__] I [__] a Nerf
gun yeah good you know you know what
it's funny the algorithm's probably
going to think this shit's fake it's
definitely not fake but check
it what the [__] you know about that you
guys call me fat in my comments and I
took great offense to that and you know
what I am now doubling down in the gym
and eating
[Music]
right thank you for getting us here safe
my brother bro tell me this car isn't
beautiful bro look at this tell me this
car is absolutely stuck my rose R fits
you pretty well right oh like the vibe
right now kind of goes with the car
right you got to put like some gangster
music it's like a gangster
car please use next
door I'm not doing it hard
enough going on I'm sorry Papa it wasn't
my fault look in all honesty I answered
the phone I did what I could how are you
what's going on you're looking Slimmer
yeah bro for real yeah I'm not just
saying that he's just saying that man he
just wants to make the s that makes you
feel that makes you feel really good
actually I'm not even going to
lie yo my dog would [__] this dog up
yeah bro this dog is mad small next to
my dog bro he was talking [__] to your
dog I was SC at this dog at first when I
started coming here yeah remember but
bro my dog is a beast next to this [__]
Bro wow
no bro our dog is just huge bro all
right let's see what they got here let's
that him this thing hey remember set
forget
talk all right boys
welcome what should we call this welcome
to Welcome to the shoe store it's my
shoe store this is
[Music]
crazy did you should get one of these
look look at
this look at this sh right here that not
that that doesn't really no this doesn't
spell gangster to you but it doesn't it
doesn't speak G to me yeah you're right
it does not speak G to you're right you
know you're you know what this speaks
pimp purple interior this is like I'm a
[__] pip I got your girl on a leash
[__] like that you know what I'm saying
yeah this P this is me right but I'm not
probably not the probably not the car
color yeah yeah this is not my type of
pimp shirt right here oh you guys want
to see Dan bazan's old 6x6 G wagon this
probably one of 25 in the world and I
think this is one of five in the United
States of America this is Dan Ban's G
wagon
[Music]
6 this might look like a regular G Wagon
in person it's definitely not but this
shit's a [__] million dollars like
literally would you pay a million dollar
for this I mean if I has million dollar
right now cash no okay exactly I mean it
is sick don't get me wrong
but I mean see confirm down was it
really
there a [__] I did that for a
reason defin that one smells like vagina
yeah this is it this is the one oh the
back was over the back was over yeah
this is this is probably seen some crazy
ass [__] like you could you can tell
it's the real one when it has the
controls up there because it has the
controls it can click a couple Buton
buttons and then the airs and the tires
will go up or down so these things can
deflate themselves and inflate
themselves so think about it you pay a
million dollar for a car and you never
ever have to self-inflate a tire that's
a good [__] deal if you ask me right
I see the value in that for a
million that's the least I can do right
you tell me that and you tell me
something else and you tell me it has a
light bar sold that's it I don't need to
know anything else so my budget for
right now is
probably anywhere from like 300 to like
400k cuz I made 400k in this trade and I
want like a nice sports car so this is
cool right GT3 I think you should
visited the GT3 realm again oh but this
is [__] gay dude shit's automatic bro
hell am I gay I the color is straight
but the transmission is gay and honestly
this has been one of my favorite cars of
all time my GT3 992 bro we abused the
[__] out of that car we blew the
transmission two times and I think we
burned through a clutch or something I
don't know every single time it would
break I would just take it to the
dealership and they would fix it cuz it
was under warranty so I don't know if
they have a big brother here like a GT3
RS maybe I don't know we got to go like
a [__] 100 cars that we got to go
through and they have an
outside but this right here if I don't
spend the full budget of the 400k I'm
going to spit it in between two cars
I'll probably buy something cheaper like
300K and then I'll buy the rest with
this right here
this is probably damn this is perfect no
no this is gay hell no this is a [__]
Aventador if you get an Aventador you
have to get either an SV or an svj don't
get this this is
like no don't get it this is ganger
right here this is the
[Music]
[__] you have a Lamborghini
Gallardo twin turbo and guess what
six-speed manual gated transmission you
hear that you hear the little
tweak beautiful see this I'll pay
$200,000 for $200,000 for all day it's a
work of art bro this is perfect look
[__] bro so you have red
interior so you have red interior twin
turbo
Lamborghini and manual transmission bro
I don't think I don't think there's more
than five of these cars in the world I
mean what more can you ask for I mean
this is a custom build obviously like
these things don't come Twin Turbo from
the factory oh [__] how the [__] did I
forget some [__]
bags yeah it's not a good thing I'm not
going to lie this is not that good I
think I've had I've had two twin turbo
Lamborghinis the first one BW the
transmission ironically enough it looked
just like this white with red and on bag
I give me a little PTSD not going to lie
my second Twin Turbo
Lamborghini caught fire but you know
what they say third times a charm so
this might be the third time right twin
turbo Lamborghini bro imagine drifting a
twin turbo Lamborghini
manual but you're a [__] pimp this is
a real pimp car BR
what not going to lie this clutch is a
little hard for
me [__] got weak legs yeah no I got you
got you got to hit like what do you mean
you can see my [__] caps right here
look at this [__] look at that you see
that yeah ites doesn't look like
mine look why why do they have the
Bugattis in the back probably so it's
harder to steal right maybe this thing
is [__] nuts right
here all right so here you have a
Bugatti Super Sport fully exposed carbon
really ganger sick orange interior this
is a nice ass interior damn you should
get this one
you do it should
I should I yeah I I think it's in budget
this probably $6 million bro what the
[__] you mean I need a daily for the
daily trade more you trade more
[__] all right so what what you
what do you got over here any brises or
anything I I need to spend 400k bro so
give me something worth 400k brises not
at the current moment cuz those things
fly off the shelf uh 400k worthy I mean
here's the thing bro I don't want to
tell you something that you already have
like the color in you have you have your
man story uh so not any Rolls-Royce
wagons honestly it would be crazy for
you to get another M wagon knowing that
you just gave up the baddest one uh I
mean like my standard is so high with
that one already that's the thing bro
are we into sports cars are we still
thinking that yeah yeah I want I want
something quick give me something fast
too quick fast all right something good
for the money fast nice sexy
new and you can fit in I I think I got
something okay you want to give me 2
minutes okay go I'll give you two
minutes all right I don't know what the
[__] he's going to bring up but it's got
to be something cool this right here I
like the Ferraris but this to me is not
worth $700,000 that $700,000 yeah this
is the enlargo or something like that
you know what's crazy I have all these
crazy cars and I really don't know much
about them you know what's crazy I don't
know anything about them but I could
drive them like nobody else how does
that work it's like if I'm straight but
I don't talk to girls by I get all the
girls and I have the best game isn't
that
concerning yeah yeah the only thing we
haven't had here is
svj or an stto that's pretty much it oh
this is [__]
gangster D the color sick holy [__]
where they have this
one hit
every oh this is [__] gang
see now now we're talking bro you know
what I'm saying yeah I know I'm dealing
with tight circumstances here tight
Corners now this is [__] but carbon
hood carbon roof carbon spoiler uh black
wheels on it obviously the the yellow is
definitely a selling point especially
whenever it comes to anything that has
to do with Porsche yeah what year is
this show 2024 if I'm not mistaken 2024
she just came in and these things they
have warranty like the other one right
all right so Porsche does 4year 50,000
miles it doesn't matter if it's a 918
GT3 or 718 so you do have a good
warranty on the car one these things so
I sold a GT3 non RS uh pts olive green
2019 the car had 71,000 Mi ago this was
a year and a half I sold the car for 169
plus dealer the window sticker on that
car was 153 oh it setting above sticker
above sticker 6 years later with 70,000
Mi the point is is that as long as you
own the car right you should be to set
and forget yeah fact what what do you
guys want for this uh you want it to be
3 to four I hate to tell you but you're
right at that cusp you're at four four
yeah four but the money is safe once
again yeah and and the good thing is is
that GT3 rs's used to run you 200,000
now the stickers on these are 250 260
290 so so the sticker on this would be
what you're probably around a 265
sticker don't hold me to it I do have to
actually pull it for you but from based
off of what I'm looking at what I've
seen before you're at a 265 sticker
somewhere around there so paying 150
above sticker it's still as crazy as it
sounds it's still not bad because if you
call Porsche right now they're going to
treat you like you're a kid walking into
a Rolex store put your order in we'll
see you if we ever get an allocation or
whatever the case is it it's just you're
not going to get it so you are paying
for to have the car now but it doesn't
matter if you're paying to have the car
now the guy who owns the car for sticker
never thinks about it ever again the guy
who buys it the way you're buying it is
still in a better position than the guy
who buys a 488 or an f8 or you know even
a Huracan for that matter these cars are
a test of time yeah yeah the yellow's
[__] sick Bro n it's [__] hot as
SI I feel like I feel like it suits me
too which is a good part and here's the
thing I know that this is a track
focused car it's supposed to make you
stay as planted and as gripped into the
ground as like possible but I know you
also have a tendency to get a little
loose so it it'll be interesting is rear
wheel drive it's rear wheel drive and
the engine sits right above the rear
axle oh easy Kate all right let's go all
right let's do itasy baby you know
what's funny I was actually telling them
earlier cuz I had a GT3 and I wanted
something like this this is perfect what
like RS or just like I want RS the only
thing that I don't like about these is
that they're not manual yeah you can't
get manual but you do have more buttons
on the steering wheel so anybody that's
inside of your car that's looking over
at you knows that this is a cockpit
driver you know I don't know what I'm
saying kind of this [__] all right let
going to
three how long does this sh last this
that
uh it said 30 minutes but the one time
that I timed it it was like 14 minutes
and some odd seconds I got it from
Target look the timer is already running
if you get everything done before like
this is fully done we'll give you the
extra 10,000 that we made on the trade
cuz we made 410,000 on the trader 4
15,000 we'll give you the extra cuz we
really don't give a [__] about but if
you if you don't get it done before this
timer runs out you got to give me that
extra Inc this sounds horrible let me
get to work all right yeah always
negotiate how how are you doing this by
the way this
can you send it to my my address my CA
yeah I'll send it to your address all
right yeah let's rock I don't Finance sh
we just well it's not a wire it's like a
wire but it's like a crypto wire does
that make sense look I've been playing
with it I've seen it go up I've seen it
go down but if it's s from you I'm going
to forget about
[Music]
it well that was easy yeah that was
pretty [__] yo this thing is gangst
you know what's funny like I saw it
online but I didn't think they had it
here in person cuz the pictures weren't
here the pictures were like somewhere
else oh yeah that was quick oh yeah I
mean what is it like 35 minutes 40
minutes they have on my M already but I
I I I was talking to Seas right now I'm
like yo we can't show them the car fully
right now because it's missing something
it's literally missing the Alex G touch
so I don't want to show you guys the car
fully until it doesn't happen have what
it's missing so we're going to take it
to my boy Kevin shop right now so he can
adjust exactly what he's missing I'm
coming back for that twin turbo Lambo
soon should even have gas yeah it has
gas oh wow they sent us a car with gas
for once bro literally every single car
bottom here has no [__] gas oh wow I
didn't see that here
earlier oh wow 4 GT that's cool know
what crazy too that we just sold like I
just sold my wagon maner and look at
this Urus manery pretty cool you know
what's funny every single car I've
always wanted I just buy it and then I
just have it like I've never like I
never test drive I never do the window
shopping I just go and buy it
hey
Alex hey I I paused it bro what I paused
it I had I had paused it the the salana
the what my CA the the 10 oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah let me get yeah let me get
your address real quick let me get let
me get your address you want me to text
it right now just give it to me right
now live
okay
[__] hell no we're not paying that
[__]
nothing all right bro we got to come
back you get you got to get the rolls
bro you got to go in the Rose bro go
oh sup you have you left your lunch back
then oh yeah my uh my protein
shake like bro look how serious this
[__] traffic
is Jes [__] you [__] you I just got a
new car all right this is probably the
only thing I hate about this car these
like these are the Y sexss look check
this out so it has the Yack GT3 RS sick
no row cage which is super whack but we
had the glow-in-the-dark
what is that is that the is that the
brand what the hell is that that's the
well I don't even know how to explain I
just wheel well wheel yes or the exhaust
but it glows up which is sick right but
then oh dude they gave me the cheap one
look at this [__] it has like a little
doesn't have forand a what the [__]
man a that's whack Dam they saw this a
bottom of the barrel ass car you know
what at least the key matches the color
matches that's pretty [__] cool right
you got to give us that whatever this is
what I hate right here getting out of
the car super uncomfortable put over
here to my boy Kevin's shop Kevin has
always hooked me up with a bunch of
wraps he did the Bugatti and like 12
hours for Aiden Ross's event he dropped
the Bugatti pink like four times or
something so let's pull up on him and
see if we can get what we need done
tonight which is very special so he has
a printer machine over there and he's
going to print out the things that that
we need and you guys see it don't make
sense I almost have to take this
dinosaur from him but you don't want to
give it to me I mean if he's not here we
could do it we just throw in the roll
always [__] hear this guy
yo
oh rain the dinosaur oh there's no one
here taking the dinosaur would be lit
right yo uh where you at I'm here at the
shop oh damn bro I have to step out I'm
like I'll be back in like 20 minutes
what do you
mean I'm not there dude but bro but like
you left the the door open bro this
place is wide open bro it's open yeah
yeah yeah oh if you're there take care
of it for me please all right I'll see
you down all right
bye I'll take care of it you
[__] oh [__] I almost broke this
damn door you know what cuz since the
doors were open something could have
went missing so when he comes in oh
dude a d
[Music]
Jesus I thought my house was bad this is
[__]
negative holy sh [__] Bro dude these
guys are down oh these God knows how
long this been in there oh my God feel
bad for these guys we might have to go
get something and put it in here for him
bro oh dude this [__] weighs like a
mother all right you give it a shot
bro oh yeah [__]
weighs usually I don't need these kind
of things I'm 6'2 but for this time this
is a very high count counter top so just
in case you know I've always wanted to
ride a
dinosaur Fern
arnia yo I'm going to shoot this [__] in
here do it bro you I should just shoot
it right into the [__] wall right
going to the AC better [__] fell
Jesus oh my
God I managed to get off from this [__]
right now
oh there's a [__]
microwave oh we're going to warm up my
food in here oh yeah I'm hungry get my
food real quick oh you think I was
playing clean lady oh well my chef lady
than you for the
boito or some zucchini you know what I'm
saying how long you know what's funny I
I don't remember the last time I warmed
something up in the microwave
respectfully right you know when you
enter a different area in life you no
longer use mic microwaves use what's
called a Waring machine have you ever
heard of one no I'm still in the
microwave bar oh okay a Waring machine
you just throw your food in there and it
warms it for you this [__] burns your
food and gives you radiation a warming
machine cost like $8,000 but you put it
in there and it slowly warms it up it'll
take like 8 minutes but it'll be fresh
not like this [__] so how do you use I
forgot how to use this bro you that was
all
[__] oh I can't add any more time
right so I just need you to do this I'm
going to show you right now I need this
though ready it's a very
complicated example right here all right
can you do
that I can try yeah I'll do my best okay
you got five minutes good Lu
[Music]
boys it would not be a proper
introduction to my new Porsche if we
don't a little bit of Dome you know what
I'm saying and I love this right here
[Music]
[Applause]
w
[Music]
we made it out honestly that's not my
first time doing that but check this
[__] the [__]
out done [__] bro
[__] like this is how you know that you
really B that life this right
here
t t and I just got the [__] car
all right we got to hide it now so can
you open up please oh my God what are
what's on the
brakes ah [__] all right we don't have
time for this we got to hide this we got
to we got to move you know we got to
[Music]